ijcaonline.org 2019-09-28

# IJCA - Privacy Policy

Call for Paper - November 2019 Edition 

IJCA solicits original research papers for the November 2019 Edition. Last date of manuscript submission is **October 21, 2019**. [Read More](https://www.ijcaonline.org/calls-)

International Journal of Computer Applications (“IJCA”) is intent on protecting your privacy. The following explains how we treat personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of IJCA products and services. 

By “personal information” we mean information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy only applies to IJCA and its employees. 

#### Information Collection and Use 

When you submit a typrescript to IJCA, we collect information such as your name, email address, institution, expertise and the like. This information may be combined with information we obtain from public sources, business partners, or other companies. Once you apply for publication, and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. We may also collect other information when you visit IJCA pages or the pages of certain IJCA partners. 

Security of such information is a high priority for us. 

For some products we may also ask for your address or credit card information. Be assured that credit card information is encrypted and stored only on secure machines. 

International Journal of Computer Applications automatically receives and records information on our server logs from the information that your browser sends to us, including your IP address, cookies, and the page you request. 

International Journal of Computer Applications uses information to customize the content you see or are notified of. We use it to fulfill your requests for products and services. We use it to improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. Other uses include storing names of the reviewers of manuscripts submitted to journals and displaying these names for editors. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure 

International Journal of Computer Applications does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with International Journal of Computer Applications under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help International Journal of Computer Applications communicate with you about offers from International Journal of Computer Applications and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of International Journal of Computer Application's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We transfer information about you if International Journal of Computer Applications is acquired by or merged with another company. 

International Journal of Computer Applications works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

#### Cookies

International Journal of Computer Applications may set and access cookies on your computer. 

International Journal of Computer Applications uses web beacons to access International Journal of Computer Applications cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with International Journal of Computer Applications products and services. 

#### Updating your Information 

We encourage you to update your IJCA information, at any time. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the International Journal of Computer Applications service, such as service announcements or administrative messages that are considered part of your International Journal of Computer Applications service, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

#### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with regulations to protect personal information about you. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy 

International Journal of Computer Applications may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your information with IJCA or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: [editor@ijcaonline.org](mailto:editor@ijcaonline.org)
